roughcountry.com 2018-11-11

# Privacy Policy | Rough Country Suspension Systems®

## Introduction

Rough Country, LLC ("Rough Country", "we" or "us") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website ROUGHCOUNTRY.COM (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

  * This policy applies to information we collect:
    * On this Website.
    * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
    * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, if any, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
    * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * It does not apply to information collected by:
    * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Rough Country or any third party (including our affiliates, subsidiaries, and parents); or
    * any third party (including our affiliates, subsidiaries, and parents), including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

This Website is offered and available to users who are 18 years of age or older and reside in the United States, any of its territories or possessions, or Canada. By using this Website, you represent and warrant that you are of legal age to form a binding contract with Rough Country and meet all of the foregoing eligibility requirements. If you do not meet all of the requirements, you must not access or use the Website. The owner of the Website is based in the United States. We provide this Website for use only by persons located in the United States and Canada. We make no claims that the Website or any of its content is accessible or appropriate outside of the United States and Canada. Access to the Website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Website from outside the United States or Canada, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, you must not access or use the Website, do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us as follows: Address: Attention Privacy Officer, Rough Country, LLC, 1400 Morgan Road, Dyersburg, TN 38024; Phone number: (731) 285-9000, ask for the Privacy Officer; Fax number: 731-285-9012, attention Privacy Officer; Email address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#fa8a88938c9b9983959c9c93999f88ba88958f9d9299958f948e8883d4999597)

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

  * We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:
    * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or ANY OTHER INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS THAT IS DEFINED AS PERSONAL OR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION UNDER AN APPLICABLE LAW ("personal information");
    * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and
    * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.
  * **Information You Provide to Us.** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:
    * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website or posting material. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us and when you report a problem with our Website.
    * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
    * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
    * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

  * **Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.**  
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:
    * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
    * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.
  * The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
    * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
    * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
    * Speed up your searches.
    * Recognize you when you return to our Website.
  * The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
    * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
    * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see the section below entitled **Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.**
    * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit Rough Country, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

Our Website may contain links to other websites. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of each website you visit. We do not control the other websites. If you have any questions about the information they collect about you, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

## Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, if any, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services . They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

## How We Use Your Information

Some content or applications, including advertisements, if any, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services . They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

  * We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
    * To present our Website and its contents to you.
    * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
    * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
    * To provide you with notices about your account.
    * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
    * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
    * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
    * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
    * For any other purpose with your consent.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

  * We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:
    * To our affiliates, subsidiaries, and parents.
    * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual or other obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
    * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Rough Country's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Rough Country, LLC about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
    * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to or not opted out of these disclosures. For more information, see the following section entitled Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
    * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
    * With your consent.
  * We may also disclose your personal information:
    * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
    * To enforce or apply our [terms of use](https://www.roughcountry.com/terms/) or [terms of sale](https://www.roughcountry.com/terms-of-sale/) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
    * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Rough Country, LLC, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

  * We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:
    * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.** If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can optout by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d1a1a3b8a7b0b2a8beb7b7b8b2b4a391a3bea4b6b9b2bea4bfa5a3a8ffb2bebc).
    * **Promotional Offers from Rough Country.** If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to Rough Country as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. Just click "edit" to change your contact information. To change your address, click on "manage." 

You may also send us an e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0474766d7265677d6b62626d67617644766b71636c676b716a70767d2a676b69) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. 

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [terms of use](https://www.roughcountry.com/terms/).

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#abdbd9c2ddcac8d2c4cdcdc2c8ced9ebd9c4deccc3c8c4dec5dfd9d285c8c4c6) or write us at: Attention Privacy Officer, 1400 Morgan Road, Dyersburg, TN 38024.

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you have chosen a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

  * **Address:** Attention Privacy Officer, Rough Country, LLC, 1400 Morgan Road, Dyersburg, TN 38024;
  * **Phone number:** (731) 285-9000, attention Privacy Officer;
  * **Fax number:** 731-285-9012, attention Privacy Officer;
  * **Email address:** [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3444465d4255574d5b52525d57514674465b41535c575b415a40464d1a575b59)

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
